<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>yf_notes on A website</title>
    <link>/ncreportist.github.io/categories/yf_notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in yf_notes on A website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/ncreportist.github.io/categories/yf_notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/</guid>
      <description>Exodus 19:1-13; 20:1-17 19:1-13 What does this passage teach us about God?
.(v10-11) It takes 2 days of concecretion for us to even see God. Even then, he will come conceiled in a thick cloud.
.(v12) Touching where is presence was would lead to instant death. Even at Israel’s most consecrated state, they were not holy enough to touch the ground he stood in
How should we relate to such a God?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/</guid>
      <description>Exodus 19:1-13 19:1-13 What does this passage teach us about God?
.
.
How should we relate to such a God?
.
.
What does he promise to do in the future?
.
.
 20:1-17 Why should we want to obey the Ten Commandments as Christians?
.
.
Which do you find especially hard to obey? What practical steps can you take to obey these commands?
.
.
  2 Samuel 7:1-17 What does David want to build (verses 1-2)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/</guid>
      <description>Exodus 19:1-13; 20:1-17 19:1-13 What does this passage teach us about God?
.(v10-11) It takes 2 days of concecretion for us to even see God. Even then, he will come conceiled in a thick cloud.
.(v12) Touching where is presence was would lead to instant death. Even at Israel’s most consecrated state, they were not holy enough to touch the ground he stood in
How should we relate to such a God?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/</guid>
      <description>Exodus 19:1-13 What does this passage teach us about God?
.
.
How should we relate to such a God?
.
.
What does he promise to do in the future?
.
.
 Exodus 20:1-17 Why should we want to obey the Ten Commandments as Christians?
.
.
Which do you find especially hard to obey? What practical steps can you take to obey these commands?
.
.
 2 Samuel 7:1-17 What does David want to build (verses 1-2)?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YF Notes: The Partial Kingdom</title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom/</guid>
      <description>INTRODUCTION  I’ve printed off all the passages that I will be refering to so you don’t have to look them up. Try your best to follow along. I’ll refer to the passage references as I go.  Genesis 12:1–3 Now the Lord said to Abram, “Go from your country and your kindred and your father’s house to the land that I will show you. And I will make of you a great nation, and I will bless you and make your name great, so that you will be a blessing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YF Notes: The Partial Kingdom (Bible Study Passages)</title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom-bible-study-passages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom-bible-study-passages/</guid>
      <description>PASSAGES: Bible Study Exodus 19:1–13 On the third new moon after the people of Israel had gone out of the land of Egypt, on that day they came into the wilderness of Sinai. They set out from Rephidim and came into the wilderness of Sinai, and they encamped in the wilderness. There Israel encamped before the mountain, while Moses went up to God. The Lord called to him out of the mountain, saying, “Thus you shall say to the house of Jacob, and tell the people of Israel: ‘You yourselves have seen what I did to the Egyptians, and how I bore you on eagles’ wings and brought you to myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YF Notes: The Partial Kingdom (Talk Passages)</title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom-talk-passages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom-talk-passages/</guid>
      <description>PASSAGES: Talk Genesis 12:1–3 Now the Lord said to Abram, “Go from your country and your kindred and your father’s house to the land that I will show you. And I will make of you a great nation, and I will bless you and make your name great, so that you will be a blessing. I will bless those who bless you, and him who dishonors you I will curse, and in you all the families of the earth shall be blessed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YF Notes: The Partial Kingdom (Talk Passages)</title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom-talk-passages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom-talk-passages/</guid>
      <description>TALK: Passages Genesis 12:1–3 Now the Lord said to Abram, “Go from your country and your kindred and your father’s house to the land that I will show you. And I will make of you a great nation, and I will bless you and make your name great, so that you will be a blessing. I will bless those who bless you, and him who dishonors you I will curse, and in you all the families of the earth shall be blessed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YF Notes: The Partial Kingdom (talk)</title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-the-partial-kingdom-talk/</guid>
      <description>INTRODUCTION I’ve printed off all the passages that I will be referring to so you don’t have to look them up. Try your best to follow along. I’ll refer to the passage references as I go. As a reminder in Gen 12 God made a promise with Abraham. He promises that Abraham would have decendants, that he would reach the promised land, that there he would recieve blessing and kings would come from him which would be a blessing to the nations under them Tonight, we will be covering around 1200 years spanning from Abraham to Solomon so a lot to squeeze in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YF Notes: Philippians 2:12-18</title>
      <link>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-philippians-212-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ncreportist.github.io/yf-notes-philippians-212-18/</guid>
      <description>Passage Philippians 2:12–18 Therefore, my beloved, as you have always obeyed, so now, not only as in my presence but much more in my absence, work out your own salvation with fear and trembling, for it is God who works in you, both to will and to work for his good pleasure. Do all things without grumbling or disputing, that you may be blameless and innocent, children of God without blemish in the midst of a crooked and twisted generation, among whom you shine as lights in the world, holding fast to the word of life, so that in the day of Christ I may be proud that I did not run in vain or labor in vain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>